Hi, you guys.
What's the matter?
Well, it's just.. It's one of these
situations that I just hate.
A massage client gave me three tickets...
to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit
at the Morgan Chase Museum.
Now you're thinking
you gotta sleep with him.
No. No. It's just that he gave me
three tickets and there are six of us.
-I'll give up my ticket.
-Me too.
Okay. That's so generous.
And I think Ross is generous too.
Great! Then it's just us girls.
-Great.
-Yeah.
So what is the exhibit?
It's mostly just photographs...
of lesbian love scenes interspersed
with video games and free sandwiches.
Oh, man!
-Hi.
Hey, Ross, listen.
Chandler got you out of going to the
lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
Thanks, but I have plans.
Elizabeth and I are going out of town.
-That's great!
-Yeah.
Think about all the money
that you're gonna make.
Why? What?
Well, her father pays you
for babysitting, right?
That's funny.
But maybe it's time to move on.
You know, let it go. Stop it!
Besides, Rachel's going out
with Elizabeth's father...
so he's much older than she is.
Looks like I'm not the only one
interested in fossils.
All that does is remind us
that you're interested in fossils.
Okay, okay.
Rachel's gonna need to yell
sweet nothings in his ear.
-Ross?
-Come on! That's funny.
Because he's gonna..
He's got, like, a hearing aid.
Because he's all old.
One second.
Okay, look, Ross.
Just so you know,
since Lizzie likes you so much...
I've accepted the fact
that you're dating her.
Really? That's great.
Yeah, but then I changed my mind.
I'm funny like that.
So I told Lizzie, now I'm telling you.
I don't want you
seeing my daughter anymore.
Look, I realize it upsets you.
Yes, it does.
But Elizabeth and I are both adults...
so I don't think there's
anything you can do about it.
I'll tell the university about
your relationship and have you fired.
Oh, a man with a plan!
The One Where Paul's The Man
This is so exciting. You can get your picture
back up on the wall of fame.
He's got all the big actors.
It was so cool when I was up there.
Me and Jim Belushi would just be
cracking up about something.
I get fired off Days of Our Lives
and he takes me down.
Now he's just laughing at me.
Look at him.
That smug Belushi bastard!
Okay. Maybe when they put
your picture back up...
they could put you by Matt Lauer.
Look at him just smiling at me.
Yeah, I know.
We'd be great together.
-So I'm back.
-Who are you?
Joey Tribbiani.
From the wall?
Okay, maybe this
will jog your memory.
Okay, anyway.
I'm ready to go back up on the wall.
I'm the star of a new TV show.
-Show me in the TV book.
-It's not on TV yet.
Well, then it's not on the wall yet.
Okay, fine. I will bring you a tape.
So, now, do you have any
of Matt Lauer's clothes?
Maybe? Just ones that
haven't been cleaned yet?
God.
I love museums.
-Soaking up all the culture.
-Yeah.
-Where do you want to start?
-The gift shop!
-And then lunch.
-Yes, but I can't eat too much.
Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight.
He said he has a big surprise planned.
Do you think maybe
he's gonna tell you he's gay?
What? No, why?
No reason. That would just be
a really big surprise, right?
You could put the aisle over here
and have the wedding ceremony over here.
I didn't know you could get married here.
This would be a beautiful place
to get married.
But I wouldn't put the aisle there.
And I would never have the ceremony there.
You'd have the ceremony
under a beautiful arch.
May I help you?
Sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt.
It's just such a beautiful space.
-Do you do a lot of weddings?
-Yes, we're popular.
There's a two-year waiting list.
Sorry.
Monica, you should put
your name down for this place.
What? Are you crazy?
I'm not getting married.
I'm not even engaged.
But there's a two-year wait.
What if you get engaged in two years?
Then you've got to wait
another two years?
That's four years.
Chandler's not gonna wait that long.
He's gonna find somebody else.
Someone who did put their name
on the list.
It can't hurt to put your name down.
If, in two years, you're not engaged,
you just don't use it.
I guess there is no harm
in putting my name down.
I'm gonna do it too.
Me too!
-Really? Who would you marry?
-I don't have anyone right now.
Oh, Phoebe.
Don't feel too sorry for me.
At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
Phoebe, that's not..
Don't even get me started on yours.
-Did you watch the tape of my show?
-I did.
-Let's get me back up there.
-You don't go up on the wall.
-What? But you saw the show.
-lt was very offensive to my people.
Dry cleaners?
Russians. It showed them
as terrorists and villains.
Okay, okay.
Look, you got Harrison Ford up there!
That's right.
Mr. Ford is a very good customer.
He brings us a lot of clothes.
You bring nothing!
Okay, that may be true.
But in Air Force One, okay,
the Russians were terrorists and evil!
And plus, he kills a bunch of them.
That's offensive to Russians.
-I've never seen it.
-You should. It's great!
This place is really beautiful.
I've been coming here since I was
a kid. This used to be my grandma's.
The only thing I got
from my grandmother was her eyes.
I mean, not her actual eyeballs.
But people say that my eyes look...
Do you wanna make out?
Sure.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Yeah. I was just thinking
about your father.
Well, whatever works for you.
No.
He just really freaked me out before.
So we have to hide our relationship
from one more person.
Big deal.
Besides, we've had fun hiding it.
Yeah.
-Yeah?
-You brought protection, right?
Why, are there, like, bears or something?
Protection. Yeah. No, yeah.
That.. That I forgot.
I can't believe I brought two cans
of bug spray and forgot that.
-I'll run to the store and get some.
-I'm the guy. I'll get it.
-Do you know where the store is?
-No.
Do you wanna ride around town
on my little pink bicycle?
A little bit.
I'll be back in 10 minutes. Get in
the hot tub and I'll meet you there.
Okay.
Oh, my God! What a great surprise!
This is such a beautiful house!
Thank you. It used to be my mother's.
This is the kitchen.
-Hey, Chandler.
-Hey, Joe.
Everybody's gotta be doing something.
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
If you're listening to this message,
we're probably screening.
Yeah, we are.
Hi, this is Hildy
from the Morgan Chase Museum.
I'm calling for Monica Geller. I wanted to
let her know that there was a cancellation.
If she's still interested in having the
Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
...it is available..
This is Chandler Bing!
Yes, the groom.
No, not the groom!
It's so secluded up here.
I know. That's why I like it here.
I feel like we're the only two people
in the world.
Sorry.
What's the matter, honey?
-Did you see a little mouse?
-No! Big bear! Big bear outside!
I think I..
-Actually, would you go check on that?
-We don't have any bears here.
Well, okay.
Would you get me a Diet Coke?
-Okay. Be right back.
-Okay.
-What are you doing here?
-I came with Paul!
-Yeah. I recognized the ankles.
-Where is Elizabeth?
-She's at the store.
-You make the girl go to the store?
-Do I know where the store is?
Hurry up. Get out.
Here you go, honey.
-Thank you!
-Diet Coke.
Ice.
I need ice.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Be right back.
Okay.
You and your ice.
Get out! Get out! Go! Come on!
No, not in there! Not in there!
He's in there!
-Did you really hear a bear?
-Go!
Here you go, honey.
One Diet Coke with ice.
Thank you.
I am so happy that you're here.
-Here I am!
-Elizabeth!
Look! Elizabeth's here!
Who were you talking to?
You guys?
How did you know we were here?
She obviously saw the tire tracks
leading up to the closed garage.
Obviously.
What are you doing here?
Did you come up here to work on
that term paper or something?
Yeah.
Well, why don't you go in that room
and do your homework?
I wouldn't do it in there.
That's my dad's bedroom.
That's your dad's bedroom.
That's your dad's bedroom!
Why are you yelling?
That Diet Coke, I think,
just straight to my head!
Hi, honey.
See you later.
Wait. I bought groceries.
I was gonna make you dinner.
Well, next time, ask!
Or at least wait for me to ask!
Hi, this is Hildy
from the Morgan Chase Museum.
-I'm calling for Monica Geller.
-Oh, no.
I wanted to let her know
that there was a cancellation.
If she's still interested in having
the Bing-Geller wedding in our facility...
it is available....
Please. He didn't hear it!
This is Chandler Bing!
No!
Can I help you?
Yeah, where's the guy who decides
whose pictures go up on the wall?
-He's not here right now.
-You're kidding me!
Make sure you tell him that Joey Tribbiani
stopped by to drop off all these clothes.
I'm an actor. I'm trying to get
my picture on the wall.
You know, there are two people
who could get your picture up there.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe you and I go out
for drinks.
You're the other one, right?
So, Lizzie, are you planning on
staying the night?
No, no. Believe me,
I'm leaving as soon as possible.
Good. Not that we don't want you
to stay. Obviously, you're welcome.
How much more homework
do you have?
I just have one problem left
that I do not know how to solve.
Rachel, maybe you wanna come
upstairs and help me figure it out?
Really?
Okay.
Okay, I'll go upstairs...
if you get me something
from the car.
What do you need from the car?
Surprise me.
Okay.
So you're gonna be in the car!
I will be upstairs!
That's where everybody's gonna be!
Just relax. Relax, Paul.
You're doing great.
She likes you.
I think she likes you. She likes you.
You know why?
Because you're a neat guy.
You are the man.
You are the man!
Still got it.
Still sexy.
You're just a love machine.
Showtime.
-Phoebe?
-Yeah?
-Have you seen Chandler?
-No, why?
The museum called and said
that there was a cancellation...
and that we could move up our
wedding. And Chandler heard.
I know. How bad is this?
Well, with a regular guy, it's bad.
With Chandler, oh, dear God!
I know! And he totally freaked out.
I can't find him anywhere!
-What are you gonna do?
-I'm never going to listen to you again.
"What harm can it do
if you put your name down?"
-Rachel said that.
-Well, Rachel's not here!
You really think she put
your picture up already?
Did she put my picture up?
You kidding, after the date we had?
I wouldn't be surprised if she put
10 of my pictures up there.
Except for the fact that I only gave her one.
I don't know where she'd get the other nine.
Here it is!
Joey, why did you sign it
"son of a bitch"?
-I didn't do that. Who would do that?
-Son of a bitch!
Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
-You! Get out of my shop!
-What did he do?
-He went out with my wife!
-Joey!
I did not go out with your wife! Okay?
I went out with her.
That's my wife!
I'm not pointing at her, no.
I'm pointing at her.
"Zelda McMurray."
Who the hell..?
How did she get up there?!
Get out!
-Well, we should go.
-Yeah.
Ross?
Elizabeth!
Okay. I'm gonna go out this window.
I'll meet you at the front door.
Tell them you're going home.
-Okay.
-Wait! No, don't go in there!
Don't go in there!
I need another soda!
Ross!
Oh, my God, Ross!
What in heaven's name are you doing here?
And that is why
we cannot see each other anymore.
Ross, you and I are gonna have
to have a little talk.
-Daddy, I..
-You're next!
Okay. I didn't know he was here.
Let me just see if I got this straight.
I tell you to stay away from
my daughter or I'll have you fired.
What you heard was:
"Take my daughter...
come up to my country house
and ruin my weekend with Rachel."
-Please, Paul. Just let me explain.
-No! Let me explain! Fired!
Okay, fine. Fine. Have me fired.
But I want you to know...
that you and I are not
all that different. I mean...
I, too, am a "neat guy."
What?
And I, too...
am "just a love machine."
-Let me show you the guest room.
-Okay.
I'm so sorry.
Please stop freaking out.
I'm not freaking out.
Why would I? A woman named Hildy called
and said we were getting married.
But that happens every day.
Honey, we were at
this beautiful place...
and I just put our names down for fun.
-I mean, what's the harm in that?
-Right here.
Please don't think I was trying
to pressure you.
-Phoebe and Rachel thought..
-Phoebe and Rachel?
So the people that knew about
our wedding before me were you...
Phoebe and Rachel, Hildy, and some
band called the Starlight Magic Seven...
who are available, by the way.
It was a mistake.
Please don't take this to mean
anything, because it doesn't.
Okay.
Really?
Yes. If it really doesn't mean anything,
because you know I'm not ready.
I know.
Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna go tell Joey
that you're back.
We were really worried about you.
And that guy that
never delivered his burrito?
He thought there was
some sort of connection.
Did she buy it?
Totally.
-So did Hildy show you the place?
-Yeah. It's beautiful.
I can't believe
you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.
I know.
-Hey, Gunther.
-Take these cappuccinos to table 11.
And that guy wants some biscotti.
I just actually came in
for a cup of coffee.
Do you still work here?
No. I quit a long time ago.
Did I forget to tell you that?
I'm sorry.
-Cool. I was gonna fire you anyway.
-Great!